contextoptional.com 2012-10-18

# Adobe Social Privacy Policy

This privacy statement (“Privacy Statement”) provides information on how Adobe Social, an Adobe company, collects, uses and shares personally identifiable information submitted by, or otherwise obtained from, you in connection with the services Adobe Social provides to our Customers (“Services”). The Services may be provided by Adobe Social on behalf of a Adobe Social licensor or Customer (“Customer”). By using or otherwise accessing content provided by the Services, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Statement. 

The Services, as part of the Adobe Digital Marketing Suite, include the Social Marketing Suite, a software-as-a-service platform for managing social media presence. The Services makes it easier for our Customers to: 

  * Launch engaging applications as well as stay attuned to social trends;
  * Develop and publish content within social networks;
  * Provide promotions and other contests within social networks; and
  * Receive reporting and usage trends of its social media presence.

## WHAT INFORMATION DOES ADOBE SOCIAL COLLECT? 

We collect the following types of information from you on behalf of our Customers:

  * Information You Provide To Our Customers: We may collect and store information you submit to our Customers who use the Services. We may also collect and store information you have shared with our Customers, e.g. from your Facebook account. The information collected may include your full name, email address, gender, photos, username, demographic information, and information necessary to provide the Services.
  * Information Collected Automatically: We collect and store certain types of usage related information whenever you interact with the Services. For example, Adobe Social may automatically collect and record information regarding your computer’s IP address, browser information, Facebook user ID, Facebook Page fan status, and browsing activities.

Such information may be shared in aggregate (non-personally identifiable) form with our partners.

##  HOW DOES ADOBE SOCIAL USE THE INFORMATION IT COLLECTS?

Adobe Social uses the information it collects on behalf of our Customers to analyze, develop and improve its products and services internally, and to provide the Services as described above. 

## CUSTOMER TREATMENT OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Adobe Social may provide personal information to Customers for whom we are providing the Services. Such Customers’ use of your personal information is subject to each of their respective privacy policies – and not this Privacy Statement. Such Customers’ privacy policies are provided to you from within the their respective applications, sweepstakes, promotions or webpages that you are accessing within the social network platform. Adobe Social does not use any of your personal information for its own purposes other than as described within this Privacy Statement. 

## WILL ADOBE SOCIAL SHARE ANY OF THE PERSONAL INFORMATION IT COLLECTS WITH OTHER COMPANIES?

Personal information about users of the Services is an integral part of our business. We neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone (with the exception of sharing your information with the specific Customer for whom we have collected your personal information – see the “Customer Treatment of Personal Information” section above). We may share your personal information as described below.

Customers: We will share your personal information with the specific Customer for whom we have collected your personal information (see the “Customer Treatment of Personal Information” section above). 

Agents: We may employ other companies to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Unless we tell you differently, Adobe Social’s agents do not have any right to use personal information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. Our agents use your personal information as described within this Privacy Statement. You hereby consent to our sharing of personal information for the above purposes. 

Business Transfers: In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, Customer information is typically one of the business assets that are transferred. Moreover, if Adobe Social, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Adobe Social goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Adobe Social may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy. 

Protection of Adobe Social and Others: We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with the law; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Adobe Social, our employees, users of the Services, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. 

With Your Consent: Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your personal information may be shared with third parties, and you will be able to prevent the sharing of this information. 

## CONDITIONS OF USE 

If you decide to use or otherwise access the Services, your use/access and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Statement and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of California state law. 

## THIRD PARTY APPLICATIONS/WEBSITES 

The Services may permit you to link to other applications or websites. Such third party applications/websites are not under Adobe Social’s control, and such links do not constitute an endorsement by Adobe Social of those other applications/websites or the services offered through them. The privacy and security practices of such third party application/websites linked to the Services are not covered by this Privacy Statement, and Adobe Social is not responsible for the privacy or security practices or the content of such websites.

##  WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION CAN I ACCESS? 

To understand your options to access and modify your personal information, Adobe recommends you review the Customer's privacy policy for whom we are providing the Service to see what options the Customer provides you. You may also be able to access the personal information you have consented to provide to our Customers through your use of the Services from within the social network you are using to access the Services. 

## CAN CHILDREN USE THE SERVICES? 

Our site and the Services available through Adobe Social are not intended for children under the age of 13. Adobe Social does not knowingly or specifically collect information about children under the age of 13.

##  CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT 

Adobe may amend this Privacy Statement from time to time. Use of information we collect is subject to the Privacy Statement in effect at the time such information is collected. If we make a material change in the way we use personal information, we will post a notice on our homepage at least thirty days prior to making any material change. Your continued use of the Services, including the use after the posting of any changes to this Privacy Statement, will be deemed acceptance by you of the Privacy Statement.

## QUESTIONS OR CONCERNS

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy on our Website, please send us a detailed message at [privacy-officer@adobe.com](mailto:privacy-officer@adobe.com). We will make every effort to resolve your concerns.

### Effective Date: May 7, 2012
